Seen, hello, Galgal Channel!
Today's project is a truth or dare game.
Yes!
Let me explain the rules briefly. Basically, you draw a question from the truth box, and if you can answer it, you answer. If you can't answer the question, you switch to the challenge box.
If you can't answer the question, you switch to the challenge box.
If you don't want to do it, you can answer it here.
If you don't want to do it, you have to answer it here.
I see.
Have you ever done it before?
No, I have not.
No, I haven't.
Yes, I have.
Have you?
Yes, I have. With friends.
With friends.
It was fun.
We could make our own decisions. There was no such thing as "I don't like this, I really don't like this.
And we only did it privately. We had to disclose it to everyone.
That's right.
To be honest, if you answer the questions, you don't know what kind of subjects are included.
I heard that everyone is a little hard-core.
I guess so.
I'd like to have fun while doing it.
Yes.
Yes, I'm sure.
Okay, let's start with you.
Is that okay?
Please do.
I'm a little new to this.
I mean, what level of the subject matter do you want to see?
I'll do it.
Which celebrity would you trade your life for one day?
I can't take this anymore.
Can I tell the truth?
The truth.
Yes.
There's too many of them.
Yes, that's right.
There are too many of them.
In other words.
Oh.
Why?
Well, you seem to be having fun all the time.
Yeah, I guess.
You seem busy, though, all day long.
But I wonder how much sleep you really get.
I'd like to trade lives with you.
Eh, it's totally fun.
I'd be scared if I was having too much fun.
I'm scared.
Then let's go.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
Oh.
What's your biggest regret?
That's a tough one. Is your biggest regret the truth or a challenge?
The hard truth.
Stiff truth?
It came out for you.
What's the truth about the hard truth?
Gachi-Truth or Truth?
It's a sidekick. It's going to be difficult.
Gachi-Truth.
I don't know if it works,
P. Is it a challenge?
Because if it becomes P, what's the point?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You are.
You're a challenge.
Yes, sir.
No, no, no, no.
I can't even talk about soon.
What?
Hey.
I introduced myself as quite the gal.
I think it's a challenge.
Isn't that good?
Okay, let's do it.
I'm Masuda Kuniya, a sophomore in college.
Lately, my hobbies are nail art.
I also like to evaluate other people's nails.
I'm counting on you.
What? You're not a bad person, are you?
My hobby is to evaluate people's nails.
People's nails?
I've never heard of that before.
My gal mindset is that of a gal with a bad personality.
Ahh...
That's not the right setting.
I'm not talking about a gal with a bad personality.
I'm talking about a gal with a bad personality.
I see.
Then I appreciate it.
It's a tough challenge.
It's a tough one.
Is there anything a member gave you that you never used?
You know, I feel bad for the girl who said that.
Maybe sometimes.
I feel sorry for them if they're serious.
I feel sorry for her if she says it's too serious.
Yes, I have.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what I'm going to do about it, whether I'm going to say it and ruin my relationship with the person, but I'm going to try.
But you say you have your reasons.
I don't know if that's going to convince them... that you're interested in them.
No, the truth is telling.
No, the truth.
Oh, uh...
The hair oil that Kira gave me...
I wanted to use that oil after I use up the one I'm using now.
I haven't used it yet.
I've been meaning to use it after I'm done with this one, but...
When did you get this oil?
Last year.
We all bought it last year.
It's November now, so it's been a year or so.
You're not going to use it?
Yes, we do.
I might have said it three times already.
And the one I got you is a pretty nice one, about this size.
Good luck.
He's so cute!
Hey!
Don't tease her.
Kira told me to be careful with it.
But I've told her to take good care of you.
So many lies.
What's the latest lie you've told?
Ho.
Yes, I have.
Truth or dare.
I'm having a little trouble coming up with one, so let's make it a challenge.
Let's make it a challenge.
I don't know what to do.
All right.
I'm glad I didn't do this.
10 seconds of serious change for the camera.
Too long.
Not long enough.
It's okay, though.
Oh, thank God.
I knew it. That's why I can't pull off the challenge.
It's not bad, is it?
I like having all this stuff in here.
Does this mean you're done with the changes?
Did you answer?
If you answered, don't do it... from here.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Oh.
No 'll
I got this one. 4.
321 Auto and person
Oh, yeah, great.
But I'm a big fan of the girls' funny faces... and I don't have a very large repertoire.
I'm not sure how much of a repertoire I have, so I'm going to go for a second go-around.
Oh, I'll cry if I get one that's a truth or a dare
No lie, I'd like you to fix the members
Of course I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, but I don't know who or what I'll say.
First of all, let's have a leader.
Okay, Momo-chan.
Oh, that?
That's great!
I thought you said it was clear.
You know, when Bamili makes a mistake.
Don't give me that look when I correct you.
Oh, I'm getting a little side-eye.
It's like you're being stretched.
I know.
I mean, seriously.
Love Cheney's chorus was really 2.5 at first!
When you say "boo-boo", you can get a Graph win with a r ashore loss.
re состо 4
I know how you feel, I know how you feel, I know how you feel
I've read what you've come to me, and I've told you that I've been working with you since the day I got here, and I know that you've been working with me since the day I got here.
I know what it's like to have it
I'll tell you what I'm going to do, I'm going to switch over until the next guy's done...
I'm going to switch to something else, and I'm going to say everything until the next person finishes, that I'm not going to say.
Yes, that's good. You have to come in.
I've never done anything natural before, so...
You don't have to, that you don't, because there's no inside.
The sexiest person here is the player.
I'm not a natural, that I don't do natural, that I don't do inside.
Oh, yeah. I did it to shake it.
Oh, yeah. No reason.
I think Claire has an image of being a neat and tidy girl... even when she wears a costume... she's a mature piece of work that we put in.
I put her in an adult piece.
Right?
I don't have any.
I'm glad you like it.
A real kissy face. Oh, man...
Oh, you don't want to challenge me? Well, I'll give it a shot, but it might be worse than that.
What are you going to do?
Put the banana down with one hand.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Banana first. Let's go for it.
I dare you.
Oh, oh, but...
It's so thick, I think it's gonna tear.
Can I use it for a costume?
Oh, this.
It's cute.
Okay, okay.
Last one?
Lap 3.
Yes, last.
Let's see the oldest selfie you have on your phone.
Once you have your own check.
Can I see it? The one I posted in my diary.
It's okay, right?
It's exquisitely disgusting.
What kind of a girl doesn't mess around?
What kind of girl?
And he put it on his own head.
I don't like it. Wait, wait.
Let me see it.
I already showed it to you.
There's a bird or something on it.
So you're the dark-haired Misaki everyone loves.
It's the happiest I've ever been.
It's hard to say "happiest.
Being allowed to do the opening performance at a baseball game against the Giants. I was so happy.
I had a bad day before the game because of a broken song, and I was sick until the day before.
I thought I wouldn't be able to perform anymore.
But I'm really happy.
I'm glad.
We were able to complete the project.
It's good.
I was happy.
I was happy. That was fine.
So, my next happy thing is to go to America.
Have you decided? Next.
I'll think about it.
But why don't you ask for it? Plastic model.
I'm looking for someone to go to America for a week.
One week is all you need.
We'll do it from here.
What is the most attractive part of your body?
Wow.
I think it's sexy.
Indeed.
Truth. Truth.
Finger.
Hey.
You have long fingers.
Indeed.
Well, good luck with the baby.
It's always been a challenge.
I've worn the same outfit for more than three days.
You want to answer that?
Same outfit.
To?
The truth?
Truth.
Oh.
Matching.
It suits you.
Then it's a good fit.
Not for three days.
Please wash this one, too.
You washed it.
Let's see what else we got.
Let's play Jangga for everyone.
Let's do that.
Whoever wins.
Whoever wins gets to play.
I win at times like this, don't I?
A lot. The one who said.
It's subtle. One more time.
Being cooed over by the opposite sex. I see. When I'm down.
When he calls me even though I didn't tell him I'm depressed.
Oh, you mean he knows.
Oh, wow.
Specific.
What's that? Kiva kiva eyes.
Kiva kiva eyes. Kiva kiva eyes.
My eyes are kiva-kiva-kiva.
What's this?
Nice. You call that a nice do-over.
It's so kubaki-kubaki-kubaki-kubaki-kubaki-kubaki-kubak.
Nice. It makes me squeamish.
If you do it like that.
Thank you very much. Finally.
Thank you for watching.
If you like this video,
channel subscription, comment, and good button.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
This time, I'm wearing Dholik's costume.